Module detail

RECON MODULES

Show IP - uses curl to perform a lookup of your external IP
DNS Recon - passive recon, whois lookup of the target. 
Ping Sweep - uses nmap to perform an ICMP echo (ping) against the target host or network.
Quick Scan - TCP Port scanner using nmap to scan for open ports using TCP SYN scan. 
Detailed Scan - uses nmap to identify live hosts, open ports, attempts OS identification, grabs banners/identifies running software version and attempts OS detection. 
UDP scan - uses nmap to scan for open UDP ports.
Check Server Uptime - estimates the uptime of the target by querying an open TCP port with hping. 
IPsec Scan - attempts to identify the presence of an IPsec VPN server with the use of ike-scan and various Phase 1 proposals. 

DOS MODULES

TCP SYN Flood - sends a flood of TCP SYN packets using hping3. 
TCP ACK Flood - offers the same options as the SYN flood, but sets the ACK (Acknowledgement) TCP flag instead. 
TCP RST Flood - offers the same options as the SYN flood, but sets the RST (Reset) TCP flag instead. 
TCP XMAS Flood - similar to the SYN and ACK floods, but sends packets with all TCP flags set (CWR,ECN,URG,ACK,PSH,RST,SYN,FIN). 
UDP Flood - much like the TCP SYN Flood but instead sends UDP packets to the specified host:port. 
SSL DOS - uses OpenSSL to attempt to DOS a target host:port. 
Slowloris - uses netcat to slowly send HTTP Headers to the target host:port with the intention of starving it of resources. 
IPsec DOS - uses ike-scan to attempt to flood the specified IP with Main mode and Aggressive mode Phase 1 packets from random source IP's. 


EXTRACTION MODULES
Send File - This module uses netcat to send data with TCP or UDP.
Listener - uses netcat to open a listener on a configurable TCP or UDP port. 